k9webprotection.com 2009-11-28

# 

                                    BLUE COAT SYSTEMS PRIVACY POLICY                     LAST UPDATED: 1.30.04
          Blue Coat Systems, Inc. (“Blue Coat”) knows that you care about how your personal information
is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our
privacy policy. By visiting Blue Coat's Web site, or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you
accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.
                                WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?
          This Privacy Policy covers Blue Coat’s treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal
Information") that Blue Coat gathers when you are accessing Blue Coat's Web site and when you use Blue
Coat services. This policy does not apply to the practices of Blue Coat that Blue Coat does not own or
control, or to individuals that Blue Coat does not employ or manage.
                   WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES BLUE COAT COLLECT?
          The information we gather from customers enables us to personalize and improve our services.
We collect the following types of information from our customers.
          Personal Information You Provide to Us:
          We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or provide to us in any other way.
The types of Personal Information collected includes: company name, company contact name and title,
company address, company contact email address, company telephone and facsimile number, company
website URL, service contract number, service level, product model number, product part number, product
serial number, MAC address, software license key number, purchase order number or sales order number,
total Web users at main location, company current proxy solutions, and special dietary requirements for
training program meals Blue Coat has highlighted the fields within the forms located throughout the Web
site that are minimally required for you to complete in order for Blue Coat to provide you with the most
complete service. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able
to take advantage of many of our special features. The Personal Information you provide is used for such
purposes as responding to your requests for certain products and services, identifying you, and
communicating with you about specials and new products. Personal Information you provide us may also
include other information when needed to provide a service you requested. For example, if you choose to
make a purchase in the Online Store area of the Web site, we will request personal information such as:
name, address, telephone number, credit card number and shipping information. When you buy a new
product, we may ask you to register your purchase electronically. When you do, we keep this registration
information on file with any information you’ve already given us on previous visits to our Web site. This
is considered your personal profile.
          Personal Information Collected Automatically:
          •    We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Web site or
               services. Blue Coat automatically receives and records information on our server logs from
               your browser including your IP address, Blue Coat cookie information, and the page you
               requested.
          •    Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and
               frequency of visitors to our site and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how
               many people watched a particular show. Blue Coat only uses this data in aggregate form, that
               is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type
               of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Web site or
               services so that we can make the Web site appealing to as many customers as possible, and
               improve those services.
                                                          1

          •    Many companies offer programs that help you to visit Web sites anonymously. While Blue
               Coat will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize
               you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.
          E-mail Communications:
          We may send email communications to you to inform you about specials, product updates, new
products, or provide you with field alerts notices and newsletters. If you do not want to receive e-mail or
other mail from us, you may i) access “Subscriber Preferences” currently located at
https://services.bluecoat.com/eservice_enu/start.swe and click the “Suppress” option for any method of
Blue Coat’s product or service-related communications you wish to suppress; or ii) click the “Unsubscribe”
option located at the end of any newsletter received by you from Blue Coat or select the option marked “I
do      not      require    further     information       at    this   time”    currently      located   at
http://www.bluecoat.com/downloads/whitepapers/internet_policy.html for news-related announcements
you wish to discontinue, or iii) simply contact Blue Coat and we will update our records accordingly.
          Personal Information From Other Sources:
          For purposes such as improving personalization of our service, we may receive information about
you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery
and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver
your next purchase or communication more easily.
          What About Cookies?
          •    Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through
               your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when
               pages in our site are visited and by how many people. Blue Coat cookies do not collect
               Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through
               cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or
               email address is.
          •    Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your
               browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your
               browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of
               ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because
               cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our Web site’s most attractive features.
        WILL BLUE COAT SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?
          Personal Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor
sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only with the subsidiaries
that are under control of Blue Coat and as described below.
          Agents: We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share
your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples include fulfilling
orders/delivering packages/sending postal mail/sending email/removing repetitive information from
customer lists/analyzing data/providing marketing assistance/processing credit card payments/and
providing customer service. Unless we tell you differently, Blue Coat’s agents do not have any right to use
Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our
sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.
          Promotional Offers: We may send offers to certain customers on behalf of other businesses.
However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to
receive these offers, please follow the guidelines listed above in “E-mail Communications.”
                                                        2

          Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of
transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if
Blue Coat, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Blue Coat goes out of
business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or
acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Blue
Coat may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.
          Protection of Blue Coat and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in
good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and
other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Blue Coat, our employees, our users, or
others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection
and credit risk reduction.
          With Your Consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal
Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.
                          IS PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE?
          Your Blue Coat account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and
security. You need to ensure authorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and
protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off
after you have finished accessing your account.
          We use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software to protect the security of your
Personal Information during transmission. This software encrypts all of the information you input.
                           WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?
          Blue Coat allows you to access the following information about you for the purpose of viewing,
and in certain situations, updating that information. This list will change as our Web site changes.
          You may access “My Settings” through the WebPower service feature currently located at
https://services.bluecoat.com/eservice_enu/start.swe to view and update your information.
                                        WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE?
          •    As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information to use, even though it
               may be needed to make a purchase or take advantage of certain Blue Coat features.
          •    You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the “What
               Personal Information Can I Access” section above. When you update information, however,
               we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.
          •    You may request termination of your Blue Coat account by accessing “Terminate WebPower
               Access”        and        completing        its       form        currently      located       at
               http://www.bluecoat.com/support/supportservices/terminate_account.html. Please note that
               some information may remain in our records after termination of your account. Such
               information may include, but not be limited to, company name, company contact name and
               title, company address, company contact email address, company telephone and facsimile
               number.
          •    If you do not wish to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please follow the guidelines listed
               above in “E-mail Communications” . Please note that if you do not want to receive legal
               notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of
               the Blue Coat Web site, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.
                                                        3

         •    As explained earlier, the majority of browsers allow you to monitor and restrict our use of
              cookies. Please note, however, that if you do not allow cookies, you will not be able to take
              advantage of some of our attractive features.
                                 CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
         Blue Coat may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is
subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used/collected. If we make changes in
the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Web site.
                                        QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS
         If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at Blue Coat site, please send us a
detailed message to privacy@bluecoat.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
                                                        4
